(Sheldon:)I will demonstrate that
I was improperly instructed in driving...
(Sheldon:)...by a woman whose lack of respect
for society borders on the sociopathic.
(Sheldon:)I will argue that the emergency
met the legal doctrine...
(Sheldon:)...of quod est necessarium est licitum,
that which is necessary is legal.
(Sheldon:)But first,
I will raise a Sixth Amendment issue.
I am unable to confront my accuser,
a non-human entity, to wit, a camera.
(Sheldon:)So to sum up, improper instruction...
(Sheldon:)...quod est necessarium est licitum,
Sixth Amendment.
(Sheldon:)My milk stool is complete.
(Judge:)-Impressive.
-Thank you.
(Judge:)Guilty. Pay the cashier.
(Sheldon:)I object.
You're completely ignoring the law.
(Judge:)No, I'm following the law.
I'm ignoring you.
(Sheldon:)Really? I would point out that I am
at the top of my profession...
(Sheldon:)...while you preside
over the kiddie table of yours.
(Judge:)Dr. Cooper, before I find you in contempt
and throw you in jail...
...I'm gonna give you a chance
to apologize for that last remark.